Guide to the Knight Biggerstaff papers, 1923-2000,
Biggerstaff, Knight papers, 1923-2000
- Series X. 1942-1944, War years at Cornell, including material on Committee on Asiatic Studies of ACLS. All material on the Chinese Army Specialized Training Program Biggerstaff directed is filed with other ASTP records in University Archives.
  - Correspondence (H-L): 1942-1944 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (M-R): 1943-1944 includes armed services' attempts to recruit Biggerstaff for service in China (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (S): 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1942-1944 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript (W): "The Westward Migration of the Chinese" includes notes and cover letter indicating publications to which it was submitted (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Notes and correspondence: 1937-1939, 1944 includes biographical sketches of famous Chinese people (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: 1936-1940 includes notes on "The Place of the Far East in the General History Curriculum" (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Series XI. 1944-1946, Six months in Division of Territorial Studies, U.S. Dept. of State and one year as Chinese Secretary of U.S. Embassy Chungking.
  - Passports of Biggerstaff and wife, Camilla, includes copy of telegram (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (A): 1944-1946 includes manuscript "The Value of Far Eastern Area Studies for Civilian Undergraduates and Specialists" (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (B-C): 1938-1946 includes correspondence with Cornell U. Press regarding Biggerstaff's publication of China: Revolutionary Changes in an Ancient Civilization and regarding Biggerstaff's status on Cornell faculty (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (D-G): 1944-1946 includes Biggerstaff's appointment as Attache in the American Foreign Service Auxiliary (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (H-L): 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (M-S): 1944-1946 includes personal history statement (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (S): 1942-1945 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (T-Z): 1944-1946 includes outline for possible book (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Series XII. 1946-1947, From June 1946, return to Cornell. Most correspondence as Chairman of Department of Chinese (later, Far Eastern and still later, Asian) Studies is in that department's files.
  - Correspondence and Book Review: 1946-1947 include description of Biggerstaff's various faculty appointments at Cornell (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (A-D): 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (G-J): 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (K-Q): 1946-1947 includes material on celebration of Princeton Bicentennial (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (R-V): 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (W-Z): 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Series XIII. 1947-1949, Includes material regarding an American Historical Association Program Committee, the Committee on Asiatic Studies of the American Council on Education, the San Diego American Institute of Pacific Relations Conference and a research trip to Nanking, China. Correspondence relating to ACLS Committee on Far Eastern Studies mainly in ACLS files.
  - Correspondence: 1947-1948 includes research and publication plans (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: 1947-1948 includes Committee on Documentary Reproduction of the American Historical Association and Committee on International Education of American Council on Education (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Book Reviews: 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Book Reviews, Speeches: 1944, 1946-1947, 1949 includes Biggerstaff's draft card and a card in Chinese (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (A-B): 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (C-D): 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1948-1949 includes applications for grants to study in China (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (G-J): 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (K-M): 1947-1949 includes substantial correspondence with and concerning John MacDonald (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (N-R): 1947-1949 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (S): 1947-1949 includes conference on The Far East and the United States sponsored by The Maxwell Graduate School of Citizenship and Public Affairs (Syracuse U.) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (T-Z): 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Series XIV. 1949-1951, Back at Cornell, includes material on Nanking trip with unedited copy of diary letters.
  - Travel Documents, correspondence: 1949-1951 includes correspondence at time of Biggerstaff's mother's death (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Biggerstaff Diary Letter from Nanking: April 23- July 30, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (A-B): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (C): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (D,E-F): 1949-1951 includes support of Owen Lattimore against McCarthy accusations (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1950-1951 includes Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, Committee on International Exchange of Persons (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (G-J): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (M): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (N-R): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (S): 1950 includes work with State Dept. Division of Research on Far East (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (S): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1950 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (W): 1950-1951 includes manuscript by Alien S. Whiting "The Soviet Offer to China of 1919 " (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (W): 1947-1951 includes extensive personal correspondence with J. B. Wood Realty Co. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Y-Z): 1949-1951 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 1949-1951 includes manuscript "The Nanking Press, April to September 1949 " (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Series XV. 1951-1955, Miscellaneous correspondence, including David Rowe attack.
  - "Rowe Row", Spring 1952 " clippings concern accusations made by David Rowe that Biggerstaff was a Communist sympathizer (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Programs: 1952, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (A): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (B): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (C): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (D-F): 1948-1949, 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (G): 1950-1955 includes notes on plan for Chinese Research Program (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1951-1955. includes: work with Harvard Committee for appointments in Departments of History and Government (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (M): 1950-1954 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (M): 1952-1955 includes proposed National Council on Asian affairs (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (N-Q): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (R): 1952-1954 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (S): 1952-1954 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1950-1955 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (W): 1951-1955 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Manuscript (Y-Z): 1953-1955, n.d. includes rough draft of manuscript on Chinese Communists (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Series XVI. 1954, Security hearing to appeal denial of security clearance by Eastern Industrial Personnel Security Board for work with Operations Research Office, a research agency for Johns Hopkins University
  - Correspondence: 1954-1956 includes Leon Lipsoji, Biggerstaff's counsel for hearing (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: 1951, 1954-1955 includes Johns Hopkins University Operations Research Office (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Personal statement, record of memberships: 1954 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Activities, Questions; 1954 table of Biggerstaff's activities and people with whom he associated during each period of his life, sample questions and answers for witnesses at security hearing (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Appendix A of Personal Statement: 1954 "Development Of My Attitude Toward Events In The Far East, 1928-1954 " (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, affidavits: 1954 includes requests for, and later, acknowledgements of, affidavits by friends supporting Biggerstaff's loyalty (Box 15, Folder 6-8)
  - Affidavits: two representative statements (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence with Leon Lipson: 1954-1956 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Leon Lipson: 1954 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with John MacDonald: 1954 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Notes: 1954 includes notes on people who wrote affidavits (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, Notes: c. 1946-1950 describe Biggerstaff's assessment of Communist China (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Notes: 1941, 1946-1948 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, notes: 1949-1952 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Series XVII. 1954, Security hearing documents
  - Transcript: "Hearing of Dr. Eugene Knight Biggerstaff" 1954 before Eastern Industrial Personnel Security Board (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Manuscripts "Material Submitted to the Eastern Industrial Security Board Appeal Division on behalf of Knight Biggerstaff" 1954 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Series XVIII. 1955-1957, Cornell department of history, related material for chairmanship (1956-1964) in that department's files.
  - Correspondence (A-B): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (C): 1953-1957 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (C): 1951, 1953, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (D): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (G): 1956-1957 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (K-L); 1355-1957 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (M): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (N-O): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (P-R): 1954-1957 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (S): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (W): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (Y-Z): 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Book Reviews, speeches: 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Speaking Engagements: 1951, 1952, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Series XIX. 1957-1960, Miscellaneous correspondence.
  - Correspondence (A): 1957-1960 includes correspondence in Chinese (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (B): 1956-1960 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (B): 1957-1960 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (C): 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (C): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (D-F): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (G): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence CM): 1956-1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (N-O): 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (P-Q): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (R-S): 1957-1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (S): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (T-V) - 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (W): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Y-Z): 1957-1960 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Series XX. 1960-1963, Miscellaneous correspondence
  - Overseers' Committee to Visit the Department of History, Harvard: 1957-1963 documents Biggerstaff's work as advisor to history dept. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (A): 1959-1963 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (B): 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (C): 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (C): 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (D): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1959-1963 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1960-1963 includes manuscript by Donald Lach (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (M): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (N-Q): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (R): 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (S): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1960-1962 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (W-Z): 1960-1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Series XXI. 1963-1965, Includes 1963 sabbatical trip to Japan, Taiwan, Hong Kong, Indonesia and Europe.
  - Calling Cards: 1963 Far East trip (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Menus, Invitations: 1963 Far East trip (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (A): 1963-1964 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (B): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (C): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (C): 1961, 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (C): 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (D): 1963-1964 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (E-G): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
  - Correspondence (M): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (N-Q): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (R-S): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (W-Z): 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Series XXII. 1965-1968, Includes Wells College Long Range Planning Committee. Correspondence as President of the Association for Asian Studies sent to Association headquarters in Ann Arbor.
  - Correspondence, report, clipping (A): 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (B): 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (C): 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (D): 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1965-1968 includes John Fairbank tribute (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (G): 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (M): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (N-O): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (P-Q): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (R-S): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (S): 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Wells College Long-Range Planning Committee 1967 (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
  - Wells College Long-Range Planning Committee 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Wells College Long-Range Planning Committee 1968 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (W): 1965-1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Y-Z): 1965-1967 includes manuscripts on non-proliferstion of atomic weapons (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Series XXIII. 1968-1972, Miscellaneous correspondence up to time of retirement.
  - Correspondence (A-B): 1968-1975 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (C): 1967-1973, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (D): 1968-1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (E-G): 1968-1970, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1968-1970, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1968-1970 ,1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1968-1971, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (M-O): 1968-1975 includes correspondence in German (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (P-R): 1966, 1968-1970, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (S): 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (T-W): 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (Y-Z): 1958-1959, 1969-1971 includes activity against Vietnam War and receipts in Italian and Chinese (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Series XXIV. 1972-1978, Post-retirement correspondence
  - Correspondence (A-B): 1970-1972, 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (C): 1970, 1973, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (D): 1971-1972, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1971-1974, 1976-1978 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (G-J): 1971-1978 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (K-M): 1970-1978 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence (N-O): 1970-1971, 1976 includes manuscript on proposed master's degree program in Asian Studies at SUNY New Paltz C1971) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (P-S): 1970-1973, 1975-1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1970-1971, 1974-1978 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (W-Z): 1970-1977 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence (A-B): 1978-1986 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence (B): 1978-1986 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence (C): 1979-1989 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence with Arun and Manashi DasGupta: 1961-1966 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Arun and Manashi DasGupta: 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Arun and Manashi DasGupta: 1975-1979 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Arun and Manashi DasGupta: 1980-1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Arun and Manashi DasGupta: 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (D): 1978-1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (E-F): 1979-1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (G): 1979-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence (H-J): 1979-1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence (K-L): 1979-1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence (M): 1979-1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (N,0): 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (P-Q): 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence (R): 1980-1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence (S): 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (T-V): 1978-1989 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (W-Z): 1980-1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Camilla Mills letters 1922 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Camilla Mills letters 1923 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Camilla Mills letters January 1924-March 1924 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Camilla Mills letters May 1924-December 1924 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Camilla Mills letters April 1925-December 1925 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Camilla Mills Biggerstaff letters April 1926-April 1927 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Camilla Mills Biggerstaff letters January 1929-April 1931 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Camilla and Knight Biggerstaff letters 1945-1946 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Notes from Knight to Family April 1949-July1949 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Scrapbook 1935 (Box 25a)
  - KB biog, biblio, photos 1957-1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Far Eastern History notes and draft 1960-1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Misc Lecture 1955-1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Rand McNally 1962-1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Rand McNally 1962-1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Dept of Far Eastern Studies 1956-1963 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Earliest Modern Gov't Schools (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs Bibles 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - China Program 1971 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Charles Peterson Promotion 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Charles Peterson Promotion 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Shadick Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Hist 257 Wells 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Hist 594 1966-1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Honors Exams 1962-1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Exams 1954-1974 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Exams 1954-1974 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Reserve Book List 1967-1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Grad Reading Course: Pre-Modern 1963-1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Hist 593 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Hist 593 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Hist 324 1962-1972 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Hist 324 1962-1972 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Hist 694 1969 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Sabbatical Trip 1963 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Sabbatical Trip 1963 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Book Draft (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Book Draft (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Book Draft (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Book Draft (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Modernization and Early Modern China 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Boatner, Maj. Gen. H.L. 1971 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - The Crisis of Minority Faculty at Cornell Cohen and Gates 1987 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Controlling from Afar Leonard (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Myth-Making and Empire Building (Comment)Watters 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Photos (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Post Cards 1960-1971 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 16th Annual Meeting 1964 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 17th Annual Meeting 1965 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 27th Annual Meeting 1975 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 26th Annual Meeting 1974 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 16th Annual Meeting Abstracts 1964 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 12th Annual Meeting 1960 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 13th Annual Meeting 1961 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 14th Annual Meeting 1962 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 15th Annual Meeting 1963 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 11th Annual Meeting 1959 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 10th Annual Meeting 1958 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 9th Annual Meeting 1957 (Box 26)
  - The Far Eastern Association: 8th Annual Meeting 1956 (Box 26)
  - 27th International Congress of Orientalists 1967 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 33rd Annual Meeting 1981 (Box 26)
  - Assiciation for Asian Studies: 30th Annual Meeting 1978 (Box 26)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 25th Annual Meeting 1973 (Box 26)
  - American Historical Association: 51st Annual Meeting 1936 (Box 26)
  - History and Theory: Studies in the Philosophy of History 1972 (Box 26)
  - Harvard Journal of Asiatic Studies 1939 (Box 26)
  - Photo album of images taken by Knight Biggerstaff: 1930s (Box 26a)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 22nd Annual Meeting 1970 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 21st Annual Meeting 1969 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 15th Annual Meeting 1963 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 20th Annual Meeting 1968 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 19th Annual Meeting 1967 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 18th Annual Meeting 1966 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 23rd Annual Meeting 1971 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 31st Annual Meeting 1979 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 29th Annual Meeting 1977 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 27th Annual Meeting 1976 (Box 27)
  - Association for Asian Studies: 24th Annual meeting 1972 (Box 27)
  - Abdulah Taufik 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Andaya 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Averill 1974-1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Brady, Sean 1964-1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Capleand, Henry 1963-1968 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Chu Nai-suon (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Connor, Alison (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Corson, Carolyn 1974-1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Connlryman, Edward 1966-1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Cushman, Jennifer 1974-1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Cushman, Jennifer 1969-1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Donovan, Peter 1969-1978 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Donovan, Peter 1969-1978 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Fenner, Bruce 1971-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Gahan, David (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Gewertz (Speisman) Margo 1964-1985 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Gewertz, Margo 1964-1985 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Hildebrand, George 1967-1984 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Hunker, David 1966-1969 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Kahn, Helen Dodson 1964 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Kaplan, Robert 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Kan Ying-Mao 1965-1978 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Laffey, Ella 1962-1984 (Box 27, Folder 23)